<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="president_number">
        <item>1st</item>
        <item>2nd</item>
        <item>3rd</item>
        <item>4th</item>
        <item>5th</item>
        <item>6th</item>
        <item>7th</item>
        <item>8th</item>
        <item>9th</item>
        <item>10th</item>
        <item>11th</item>
        <item>12th</item>
        <item>13th</item>
        <item>14th</item>
        <item>15th</item>
        <item>16th</item>
        <item>17th</item>
        <item>18th</item>
        <item>19th</item>
        <item>20th</item>
        <item>21st</item>
        <item>22nd</item>
        <item>23rd</item>
        <item>24th</item>
        <item>25th</item>
        <item>26th</item>
        <item>27th</item>
        <item>28th</item>
        <item>29th</item>
        <item>30th</item>
        <item>31st</item>
        <item>32nd</item>
        <item>33rd</item>
        <item>34th</item>
        <item>35th</item>
        <item>36th</item>
        <item>37th</item>
        <item>38th</item>
        <item>39th</item>
        <item>40th</item>
        <item>41st</item>
        <item>42nd</item>
        <item>43rd</item>
        <item>44th</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="president_name">
        <item>George Washington</item>
        <item>John Adams</item>
        <item>Thomas Jefferson</item>
        <item>James Madison</item>
        <item>James Monroe</item>
        <item>John Quincy Adams</item>
        <item>Andrew Jackson</item>
        <item>Martin Van Buren</item>
        <item>William Henry Harrison</item>
        <item>John Tyler</item>
        <item>James Polk</item>
        <item>Zachary Taylor</item>
        <item>Millard Fillmore</item>
        <item>Franklin Pierce</item>
        <item>James Buchanan</item>
        <item>Abraham Lincoln</item>
        <item>Andrew Johnson</item>
        <item>Ulysses Grant</item>
        <item>Rutherford Hayes</item>
        <item>James Garfield</item>
        <item>Chester Arthur</item>
        <item>Grover Cleveland</item>
        <item>Benjamin Harrison</item>
        <item>Grover Cleveland</item>
        <item>William McKinley</item>
        <item>Theodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>William Taft</item>
        <item>Woodrow Wilson</item>
        <item>Warren Harding</item>
        <item>Calvin Coolidge</item>
        <item>Herbert Hoover</item>
        <item>Franklin Roosevelt</item>
        <item>Harry Truman</item>
        <item>Dwight Eisenhower</item>
        <item>John F. Kennedy</item>
        <item>Lyndon Johnson</item>
        <item>Richard Nixon</item>
        <item>Gerald Ford</item>
        <item>Jimmy Carter</item>
        <item>Ronald Reagan</item>
        <item>George H. W. Bush</item>
        <item>Bill Clinton</item>
        <item>George W. Bush</item>
        <item>Barack Obama</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="president_years_of_service">
        <item>1789-1797</item>
        <item>1797-1801</item>
        <item>1801-1809</item>
        <item>1809-1817</item>
        <item>1817-1825</item>
        <item>1825-1829</item>
        <item>1829-1837</item>
        <item>1837-1841</item>
        <item>1841-1841</item>
        <item>1841-1845</item>
        <item>1845-1849</item>
        <item>1849-1850</item>
        <item>1850-1853</item>
        <item>1853-1857</item>
        <item>1857-1861</item>
        <item>1861-1865</item>
        <item>1865-1869</item>
        <item>1869-1877</item>
        <item>1877-1881</item>
        <item>1881-1881</item>
        <item>1881-1885</item>
        <item>1885-1889</item>
        <item>1889-1893</item>
        <item>1893-1897</item>
        <item>1897-1901</item>
        <item>1901-1909</item>
        <item>1909-1913</item>
        <item>1913-1921</item>
        <item>1921-1923</item>
        <item>1923-1929</item>
        <item>1929-1933</item>
        <item>1933-1945</item>
        <item>1945-1953</item>
        <item>1953-1961</item>
        <item>1961-1963</item>
        <item>1963-1969</item>
        <item>1969-1974</item>
        <item>1974-1977</item>
        <item>1977-1981</item>
        <item>1981-1989</item>
        <item>1989-1993</item>
        <item>1993-2001</item>
        <item>2001-2009</item>
        <item>2009-2017</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="presidents_party">
        <item>No_party/Federalist</item>
        <item>Federalist</item>
        <item>Democratic-Republican</item>
        <item>Democratic-Republican</item>
        <item>Democratic-Republican</item>
        <item>National-Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Whig</item>
        <item>Whig/Democrat</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Whig</item>
        <item>Whig/Democrat</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat/Free_Soil/Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
        <item>Republican</item>
        <item>Democrat</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="presidents_facts">
        <item>"Despite popular myth, his dentures weren`t made of wood. They were made of hippopotamus ivory, bone, animal and human teeth, lead, brass screws and gold wire."</item>
        <item>"John Adams visited Shakespeare`s home in Stratford-upon-Avon with Thomas Jefferson, before they hated each other`s guts."</item>
        <item>"Jefferson invented the swivel chair!"</item>
        <item>"Our smallest president stood at 5`4`` and weighed around 100 pounds. Aw!"</item>
        <item>"Due to his penchant for outdated Revolutionary War era dress, Monroe`s nickname was "The Last Cocked Hat.""</item>
        <item>"The son of our Jefferson-hating second president, John Quincy Adams was known for skinny dipping in the Potomac River every morning."</item>
        <item>"He was involved in an estimated 100 duels, usually because someone said something negative about his wife."</item>
        <item>"Van Buren holds the title of the first president to be born in the U.S."</item>
        <item>"Harrison gave the longest inauguration speech ever (8,445 words over 90 minutes) on a wet, cold day in 1841. He fell ill soon thereafter and died 33 days into his presidency."</item>
        <item>"The first vicnepredidentt to become president, paving the way for the 25th Amendment, which made the line of succession official."</item>
        <item>"Every party has a pooper and that pooper was Polk. He banned booze, card playing and dancing from the White House."</item>
        <item>"Got Bacterial infection from either wild cherries or the cold milk he washed it with, leading to his death a few days later."</item>
        <item>"Fillmore married his schoolteacher (oo la la!)."</item>
        <item>"His penchant for the hooch might explain his alleged arrest for running over an old lady with his horse."</item>
        <item>"Buchanan holds the record of being the only bachelor to be president, although he may not have been truly single."</item>
        <item>"In addition to abolishing slavery, Lincoln  was also  a bartender and a really good wrestler. He won all but one of approximately 300 matches."</item>
        <item>"The first president to be impeached!"</item>
        <item>"Grant couldn`t stand the sight of blood, which is ironic considering his Civil War history and he dismantled the Ku Klux Klan during his presidency (they unfortunately regrouped decades later)."</item>
        <item>"The victor of one of the most disputed elections ever; he lost the popular vote by 250,000, but eked out an electoral college win by a single vote."</item>
        <item>"Garfield was ambidextrous and could write in Greek with one hand and in Latin with the other at the same time!"</item>
        <item>"Sold off 24 wagon loads of historical relics, including a pair of Lincoln`s pants and one of John Quincy Adams` hats to pay for redecorating the White House."</item>
        <item>"Wmarried at the White House to the youngest First Lady ever at the age of 21."</item>
        <item>"He was the first president to have electricity in the White House and was so scared of being electrocuted that he refused to touch the light switches and was known to go to bed with all the lights on."</item>
        <item>"Cleveland is the only president to hold the office for two non-consecutive terms."</item>
        <item>"McKinley considered carnations his good luck charm and wore them everywhere."</item>
        <item>"A toy maker mad him unforfettable by producing "Teddy Bears" in his honor, after news got out that Roosevelt refused to shoot a bear cub on a hunting trip."</item>
        <item>"Taft is most known for his waist line and supposedly getting stuck in a bathtub (historians say this didn`t really happen)."</item>
        <item>"He was left partially paralyzed and almost blind, but stayed in office until 1921. He relied heavily on his wife Edith Bolling Galt, a descendant of Pocahontas (!!!), for help, leading to her nickname as the "Presidentress.""</item>
        <item>"He messed around with a woman named Nan Britton, who wrote a book called "The President`s Daughter" about how her daughter was Harding`s."</item>
        <item>"Coolidge had two raccoons named Reuben and Rebecca, who would sometimes run around the White House."</item>
        <item>"Hoover and his wife lived in China for a time and would speak Mandarin in the White House when they wanted to have a private conversation."</item>
        <item>"FDR was obsessed with his dog, Fala, the only pet to be immortalized in a presidential memorial alongside his owner."</item>
        <item>"He met his wife, Bess, in Sunday school when he was six. Talk about locking it down!"</item>
        <item>"Ike changed the name of FDR`s presidential Maryland retreat from Shangri-la to Camp David."</item>
        <item>"In 1957, Kennedy was awarded a Pulitzer Prize for his book, Profiles in Courage."</item>
        <item>"The Civil Rights Act, which Johnson signed into law on July 2, 1964, was the most comprehensive and far-reaching legislation of its kind in American history."</item>
        <item>"Nixon loved to bowl so much that he had a one-lane alley put in the basement of the White House."</item>
        <item>"Ford is the only president to never be elected by the voting public to president or vice president (first Vice President Spiro Agnew resigned, followed shortly thereafter by Nixon)."</item>
        <item>"Carter appeared in an unlikely publication: Playboy. Carter refused to apologize."</item>
        <item>"Reagan regularly consulted with an astrologer, Joan Quigley, before making decisions and scheduling big events."</item>
        <item>"Bush inspired a Japanese word, "Bushusuru," which means "to do the Bush thing." What thing, you ask? Vomiting in public, as Bush did all over the Japanese Prime Minister in 1992."</item>
        <item>"Bill has two Grammys (one for Best Spoken Word Album and another for Best Spoken Word Album for Children). Future EGOT?"</item>
        <item>"W. was his high school`s head cheerleader."</item>
        <item>"His experience working at a Baskin-Robbins as a teen has made him hate ice cream. In high school, he used to be called "O`Bomber" for his basketball skills."</item>
   </string-array>
</resources>